myteam11.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy of MyTeam11

## PRIVACY POLICY

The privacy policy and personal information safety related to the services and Fun Features offered by MyTeam11 are defined in this document.

"MyTeam11 is neither associated with nor claims any responsibility or official status with any of the official or non-official sportsperson or team. Further, the MyTeam11 platform is not associated or affiliated with any private or government cricket leagues/tournaments in any manner unless stated by the organization itself. MyTeam11 do not promote, support or encourage betting or gambling in any form."

Myteam11.com is the forerunning brand of MYTEAM11 FANTASY SPORTS PRIVATE LIMITED (further referred as “Myteam11.com,” “myteam11.com” or “MyTeam11”). Myteam11.com is basically a cricket portal which enables its users to play online fantasy cricket game.

The individuals using the services or Fun Features provided by MyTeam11, or participating in the any of the program(s) or contest(s) organized by MyTeam11 is bound to comply by these Privacy policies defined by MyTeam11.

Myteam11.com ensures to maintain and protect the privacy of the individuals using the services, Fun Features and contest(s) offered by MyTeam11.

MyTeam11 offers a variety of Fun Features to enhance the user experience which can be studied in details in the “ **About Us**” section of our website. The individuals using the Fun Features and services provided by MyTeam11 are required to create and register an account with MyTeam11 in order to avail the services offered by Myteam11.

## REGISTRATION

The individuals wishing to use the services, Fun Features and participate in the contest(s) organized by MyTeam11, need to complete the registration process of myteam11.com. 

MyTeam11 registration process requires the user to submit and verify certain documents for providing personal and contact information to the MyTeam11 platform. The documents required for creating and registering an account with MyTeam11 include:

  * ID

  * Email

  * Mobile Number

  * Password

  * Date of birth

## USER INVITATIONS

The individuals using the services and Fun Features provided by MyTeam11 can invite other individuals who can be either non-registered or already registered users of MyTeam11 using their email address or Facebook usernames for participating in any of the Fun Features or contest (a) organized by MyTeam11.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to myteam11.com at [support@myteam11.com](mailto:support@myteam11.com) or by normal/physical mail addressed to: **MyTeam11 101, Nemi Nagar Ext Vaishali Marg, Vaishali Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan, 302021**   
The personal or contact information provided by the users can be used by MyTeam11 to either contact the user or to invite the user to register with myteam11.com and participate in the Fantasy Games/Fun Features offered. In order to avail the services provided by MyTeam11, the users will have to comply with the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions for participation in any of the Contest(s), Program(s) and Fun Features offered by MyTeam11.

## USE OF INFORMATION:

The user information collected and stored by MyTeam11 is primarily used by MyTeam11 to provide its services and Fun Features to the users. The user information collected by MyTeam11 is associated with the contest(s), fantasy games or Fun Features that the user wishes to play or participate.

Further, the collected information can also be used for the following purposes:

  * For offering information demanded by the users regarding Fun Features, program(s) and contest(s) organized by MyTeam11.

  * To enhance the user-experience and Fun Features offered to our users.

  * Password

  * For informing or notifying our users about any sort of changes, modifications or 

improvements to our website, services or Fun Features that may affect our service. The user information collected and stored by MyTeam11 can also be shared with advertisers or third parties to get to know about the site visitors and site traffic. 

MyTeam11 reserves all the rights to disclose or share the personal information provided by the user to MyTeam11 with third parties in order to promote fraud protection and reduce the credit risk to minimal levels, providing services requested by the User, complying with legal process, and ensuring security related to our services.

MyTeam11 ensures its users to notify them prior using their personal or contact information (like username, email address) for any purpose. In an event wherein any user does not want MyTeam11 to use or share the user data, the users will have the opportunity to withhold their consent for their use other than as listed above.

## COLLECTING INFORMATION/USE OF COOKIES:

An HTTP cookie (also called web cookie, Internet cookie, browser cookie or simply cookie), is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in the user's web browser while the user is browsing. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the user's previous activity.

MyTeam11 shall use cookies and similar electronic tools in order to collect user information for enabling us to provide services and Fun Features to the users. A unique number called User Identification (User ID) is assigned to the web browser of the user in order to assist MyTeam11 in understanding the individual interests of different users. Despite assigning User ID or unique numbers to different users availing the services and Fun Features provided by MyTeam11, myteam11.com has no way to know or decide who the User is. The user cannot be identified until and unless he/she voluntarily identifies himself/herself through the registration process.

A cookie can be defined as a piece of data stored on the hard drive of the user’s computer system that enables MyTeam11 to recognize the user, and the path user follows while visiting Myteam11.com from one page to other. The utilization of cookies assists MyTeam11 in customizing the website as per the interests of different users helping MyTeam11 to understand how different users use the services and Fun Features provided by MyTeam11 alongside playing the Fantasy Games, such that the information can be used for enhancing the services, website, Fun Features and Contest(s) provided/organized by MyTeam11.

The cookies used by MyTeam11 do not save, store or scan any personal information from the computer system of the user. The personal information stored in the form of cookies is attained through the user’s act, which can be defined as a user’s own input on a website's form. In an event wherein the third party advertisers associated with MyTeam11 assign their own cookies on the computer system of a user when a user intentionally/unintentionally clicks on their ad banners, MyTeam11 shall not be held responsible or liable.

In an event wherein an individual using the services or Fun Features provided by MyTeam11 visits www.myteam11.com, then the web servers associated with myteam11.com will automatically collect limited information relative to the computer system of the user, including User's IP address, (User's IP address is a numerical label assigned to each device participating in a computer network that uses the Internet Protocol for communication. This number allows computers attached to the Internet know where to send data to the User -- such as the web pages viewed by the User. It is similar to that someone needs your mailing address to send you a letter). The IP address of the user’s computer system is not responsible for sharing any sort of personal information of the user. The user information collected by MyTeam11 is used for delivering or providing the content and services demanded by the users. In addition, this information helps MyTeam11 in enhancing or upgrading the services, Fun Features or website of MyTeam11 in alignment with the user interests. Further, the collected or stored information helps MyTeam11 to analyze the site traffic and to let advertisers know the geographic locations of myteam11.com's visitors which ultimately signifies popularity.

There are various links and redirecting URLs’ to the third-party website on myteam11.com. The third-party websites have different privacy policies defined that are beyond the control of MyTeam11 and in this regard, MyTeam11 shall not be held responsible for any loss, or inadequate usage of user information. In an event wherein any user clicks on the redirecting URLs to third party websites and leaves the myteam11.com's servers (the User can check the URL shown in the location bar of User's browser to know where he/she is or to know the location) the usage of any information provided by the user will be governed by the privacy policy of the site’s operator which the user is visiting which might differ from the privacy policies defined by MyTeam11. In an event, the user is unable to visit the privacy policy page from the homepage of the site being visited by the user, then the User may contact the site directly for more information.

The user information collected and stored by myteam11.com can be shared with the third party advertisers associated with MyTeam11 to assist them to understand the preferences of the users who visit the website and also confirm the value of advertising on myteam11.com. The user information shared by MyTeam11 with the third party advertisers associated with myteam11.com is usually in the form of aggregated statistics of traffic on various pages within myteam11.com.

## INFORMATION SECURITY:

All the user information collected and stored by myteam11.com’s web servers is the one which the user voluntarily submits. In addition, information submitted by the user is safely and securely stored within the myteam11.com-controlled database. The databases used by myteam11.com for storing the user information are protected by a firewall. The access to such servers is strictly limited and is password-protected in order to ensure a safe and secure storage of the user’s personal information. However, MyTeam11 does not guarantee the security of the databases due to the fact that despite adopting various effective security measures, no security system is impenetrable or inaccessible. In addition to this, the user information can be obstructed amid the transfer of the information over the internet. Further, any sort of user information shared by the user amid the time of discussion over the site is public and can be easily accessed by anyone with Internet access.

Myteam11.com holds all the rights to review, modify or change the privacy policies of the site with changes or modification in the context of the internet policies. However, the usage of user information collected by myteam11.com will stay consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

Myteam11.com comprises of third party advertisers that provide ads to the users at the time of their visit to myteam11.com. These third-party advertisers might use the user information (excluding personal details like name, address, phone number etc.) for analyzing and tracking the user visits to this and other websites, in order to understand the user interests, and then provide goods, services and other advertisements on the basis of user interests. MyTeam11 shall not reveal, share or disclose the personal information or the identity of the user collected at the time of registration with these third party advertisers. Several fraudulent emails, websites, blogs etc. often including the photos, logos, links, content or any other information associated with MyTeam11, may or are circulating on the Internet and claim to be from or associated with myteam11.com. Such fraudulent emails, websites, blogs etc. might often ask the users to share their personal details including (but not limited to) like login name, password etc. In addition these fraudulent websites, emails, blogs etc. might even demand the credit or debit card details of the user by convincing the users that they have won a prize or bonus amounts. Such emails, blogs, websites etc. are not associated with MyTeam11 in any manner, and MyTeam11 shall not be held responsible in an event any of the users reply to such emails or blogs or share any information with them. Myteam11.comstrongly recommends the users not to trust, and respond to such ails, blogs, websites etc. and also not to share any credit /debit card details with them.

Any doubts or comments with respect to this Privacy Policy can be sent to myteam11.com at support@myteam11.com or by normal/physical mail addressed to: **MyTeam11 101, Nemi Nagar Ext Vaishali Marg, Vaishali Nagar, Jaipur, Rajasthan, 302021.**

## COLLECTING USER INFORMATION FROM SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS

We at MyTeam11 collect certain user information from social media platforms such as Facebook and Google in order to help the users create an account on the MyTeam11 platform. The information collected by MyTeam11 is stored in the database of MyTeam11 and further displayed in the Profile section of the user in order to provide an identification of the user to both the platform authorities and other users of the site. The information collected from the aforementioned social mentioned platforms include:

**Id** : The “Id” here refers to a unique identification number assigned to each of the users availing the services of these social media platforms. The ID collected by the MyTeam11 platform is used to identify the user visiting and availing the services provided on MyTeam11 platform. 

**Email Id** : The email id of the user using Facebook and Google services is collected by MyTeam11 as soon as the user registers on the platform using either of the social media platforms. The email id collected by MyTeam11 from such social media platforms is used to be displayed in the user profile section of the individual using MyTeam11 services.

**First Name & Last Name** : MyTeam11 also collects the First name and the last name of the individual registering on MyTeam11 through the aforementioned social media platforms. The first name and last name collected is also used to be displayed in the user profile section of the individual to validate the user as a verified user of MyTeam11. 

**DATE OF BIRTH** : The MyTeam11 platform additionally collects the Date of Birth of the user when the individual registers on the platform using either Facebook or Google. The Date of Birth collected by MyTeam11 is used to identify the age of the user and testify whether the user registering with the platform is an adult & liable to use the services provided on the platform.
